[Music]
if you asked a random American on the
way to the bank where they're going to
deposit a social security check uh into
a government insured account uh before
hanging out in a public park and
debating whether to go to the county
library or the city zoo and which
federally funded highway to take uh to
either or both uh we'd still be like
socialism not a
fan the militia group that occupies
mathor wildlife refuge and burns Oregan
is tired of receiving dildos in the mail
why do we want dildos and when do we
want them now okay ladies you you you
just can't occupy a a federal building
because you're hoping to get dilds
that's not how this whole thing happened
actually that's exactly right Larry you
got to have a real cause all right like
burning public land with no consequences
yeah we earned our dildos God damn it I
voted for bu because he was black I make
no apologies for that right that's why
no John it's
true
f